In today's video, I am going to give you the
intraday position for tomorrow
about III Laird.
Here we can see III Laird has closed
around 189 and it can be seen that it had gone up quite a bit
and then again
Drest Kili
is seen falling down here and there is a chance that it may go up again, so
I am giving you a buy
recommendation again and the previous
recommendation has already hit the target, if
you want you can go and checkout the video,
if we talk about today's performance,
here we can see that
today's performance went down
to 1846 and today's high went up
to 885, if we talk about within a year, the
low here is
1353 and the high went up to
₹2000000, the people from the grow side have
said here that you can buy at 64, you
can hold at 23 and sell at 14  But this is totally
from their side, so if I
give you a recommendation, then you can come and buy it, at
almost how much, so let's assume here that
you can come and buy at
1800 40, otherwise
you can buy at the current market price above the same price which has closed,
around 1800 65, you can come and buy, it is going to be a buy
and its close will be around how much,
its close will be till 1840 and the target is
amazing, come and see the target here, the
first target will be till 1904 and the second
target is
910, both these targets can be achieved tomorrow if
you want, just analyze and do
not trade because
if you trade in the beginning then there is a
very high risk of losing money and the
recommendation I am giving is totally up to you whether
you trade or not, if
you trade then do it at your own risk,
otherwise just for knowledge you should come and
see how the movement is going and
what kind of data you get.  We are going to talk
about Oil India.
I am giving you recommendations for the swing in this Oil India share. Stay tuned to
this video in
which I will tell you the complete details of
how you can come and trade. It
can be seen that this share came to almost 4000 and
closed at 91.5. So it can be seen that
today's performance, if
we talk about it, then here
it went low at ₹ 73.7 and if we talk about the high, then
[music] it
closed at 494.45 paise and went up to the high
and if we talk about the 52 week low, then it was at
24150 paise and the high went up to ₹ 7767 in 52 weeks, that
means within one year,
you can trade within it if you want.
If it comes near 200 again, then
you can come and buy it. If it goes to 700, then
you can come and sell it. If you come to the low
and high of one year  If you look at it, you get a
good idea. If we talk about it,
there is a recommendation from Groww's analyst at 87 to buy.
And if I come and
give you a recommendation from my side, then it will be for
educational purposes only. So you
can come and swing trade here, that is, you
can hold it for 5 days and buy this
stock around
1.75. Okay, and the SL that you can keep
here is
4470 and its target is going to be
495, the first target and the second target will be
505. So these are two targets. We work in the ratio of 1:1 or 1:1:
5. We are going to talk
about Laser and Turbo Mine Tree. It can be seen that this stock has
closed today at around
8815 and it can be seen that it can be seen
moving quite well here.
If we talk about its performance, then
today's
performance can be seen.  It was around
5661 and the high went up to around 900. If
we talk about the 52 week low,
it was ₹
513 and the high went up
to 6767. So you can see that the range within a year is a
good gap. If you want, you
can fulfill it by buying for the long term.
But today we will
talk only about intraday trade. So
if we talk about Groww, here the
recommendation is coming at 44 that you
can buy and sell at 33. So I will
give you my own position. So you can come and buy it
around 5763 and its sale is going to happen almost
till 5700. And if we talk about the target, then
its target is going to be
5834. The first target is ₹
584. We work in the ratio of 1:1 or 1:1.5.
This video is only for
educational purposes.  If you trade, do it at
your own risk.
In this video, we are going to talk
about SRF shares. It can be
seen that SRF shares
closed at 23505 paise. If you
stay with this video, I will
tell you how you can come and trade here.
Tomorrow can be seen. If we
talk about its performance, then
here we can see that today's low was
around
89.1 and the high went up
to 2719 and you can say that the 52-week low was
89 here and the high was
2693. So here you can say that there is a
gap of almost ₹ 7700 within 52 weeks, that is,
within 1 year, how much return has been given by
mixing high and low. So, if we talk
from the side of Groww's analyst, then he
came and told here that there is a buy recommendation at 69. It is
your choice if you come and
follow him.  If you want, you can follow, so
I recommend you to come and
buy it, I will
write the approximate buy price,
you can buy it around 22344 and it is going to be close,
you should come and keep it
till 2300 ₹ and the target is going to be from
2370 to
2378, there are two targets here, 1:1 or 1:1.5, in
today's video we are going to talk
about Nestle India
and the price target prediction of Nestle India
for tomorrow,
you will get information about the same in this video, it can be
seen that as soon as the market closed, it
stopped here at around 2200 19.90 paise and if we talk
about its position, that is, today's performance, then
you can see here that the low
here went to around
29455 paise today and the high went to around
22224 here  Till now there has been a good
movement here, you can say that there has been an
up and down of almost 100 points,
110 points and if we talk
about the 52 week low, then see, it went
down to 21445 here and the 52
week high here is
2778, so you can say that the share of Nestle India has
not fallen that much
and it can be seen that the analyst of Groww has
recommended a buy at 75,
but if you want to do intraday, then you
can come and buy this share,
I will give you the target, you should come and buy it, the buy date is going to be
around
22215 and its ASAL will be almost
2185 and its target is going to be from 2245 to
2265, okay these are two targets in the ratio of 1:1 or 1:
1.5, so if you have any doubt
So, baby, you can come and ask in the comment section below. If
you want more such videos, then
subscribe to our channel
and there are many videos in our channel
which can help you in
share market trading. I hope
you have got some new information and this
video has been made only for educational purpose.
Thank you for watching this video guys.
Thank you.